Downloaded @ subs4free.club
*Subtitle production ‖ iBoy. Enjoy it!*
I don't like this one
You know
Yeah
Now the shot is short
Hi
Reggie
Laura
hi
Hello
Nice to phone meet you in this incredibly embarrassing way
Ohh you know no
no problem
Ohh this is what I get for picking a trendy place with no sign out front
Yeah
Why do they do that
I don't know
I've only been in the city for a few months away
Ohh
Wow
Yeah
well it's very cool restaurant
Is it Hudson
Yes
I on Hudson
I don't know
Shit
I know
Walking towards Hudson
I'm so
so sorry
This is not the first impression I wanted to make on a college professor
Ohh
associate professor
And it's just film studies
So you're safe
Health studies
That's cool
You say that
but try teaching a class on 20th century slashes to a heap of hungover 19 year olds
Flashes
huh
What's your favorite scary movie
Not that one
So white slashes
You know
I think it's interesting
You can really examine the culture of the moment by looking at the tropes at the time
Like the masked killer
the final girl
The different rules
Don't split up
Don't help
Don't answer the phone
Exactly
Yeah
exactly
It's all cliche
but out of those cliches comes an opportunity for outside art
I've always felt the voiceless
you might say
yeah
I'd be more of a romcom guy
to be honest
OK
they got on Hudson
What color is the outside of the restaurant
I I think it's red
I don't see anything red
I am
I could be wrong and let me just let me know
Have a little look see
Yeah
it's definitely red
not seeing anything red here
So you're on Hudson
Oh oh crap
I'm still a block over
Oh
it looks like there's an alien cut through
Is the restaurant near an alley
Yes
yes
there is valley
Perfect
OK
I'm coming down the oven
I don't see you
Wait
really
Are you sure
There's some dumpsters about halfway down
You see that
I don't see you
Yeah
see you either
This is creepy
right
A little bit
20 century slashers
huh
Yeah
I usually are walking towards on something
I'm sure
Oh wait
I think I see you
Can you can you wait
Can you send me
The person I'm looking at isn't waving
they're
Staring at me
Teacher
OK
this is weird
Now they're moving towards me
Are you OK
Oh
shit
He's following me
I don't
I don't see anybody
Shit
he's after me
Where are you
He's kind of name
He's got a knife
That's not the worst fucker
You teach a class about slashers and you still walked into a dark alley alone
That's not funny
No
It's not
Now I see something red
Yeah
no
I wouldn't
Tara
listen
are you going to come to the KB party
Well
if you finish this Spanish project in time
yes
we will
Your sister coming
What about fight
First time for everything
Not tonight though
Can't convince her
No
that's not my problem
That's yours
Give me a drink
Alright
I'll see you
Ohh
Right
Rag
I'm sorry
OK
I I just got massive blue balls and I had to practice
Please don't be mad
How mad are you
Ohh
I'm not mad Jason dude
We said we wouldn't use the voice on each other
he said
A lot of things
This is Greg
right
Who else would it be
Where are you
I want to tell you about it
Ohh by the way
We should go to that frat party terrorist going ohh
I'd like none on the phone man
And seriously
turn off the fucking voice modulator
I'm just trying to give the voice right
You got to have your practice
I get mine
Whatever
Just tell me what it felt like
Maybe I'll come out
I know you're not here
Humor me
I'm fine
It was even better
and being inferior could have imagined
Right when the knife went in her
it's like
She wasn't human
Anymore
Just an animal
And
Every time it went in
She was
Less
The last human
Man
She was
Just meet
But she wasn't just meet Jason
She was a person
our film professor
Yeah
well
Fucker
Ah
she gave me a C minus on my jello paper
Is that why you killed her
Because of the C minus
Who's next year
Grade school vice principal
You know who's next
Why are you being like this
Come on
Jason
how long have we known each other
You tell me
Eight years
We met in junior high in Atlanta
I just want you to tell me why you think you're doing this
In your words
we're finishing Richie's phone
That's right
By killing Sam and Tara
Why are you fucking with me
Why won't you tell me where you are
Why do you keep asking me that
I already told you
I'm here
Let's play a game
Now warmer
Colder
Come on
find me
And then we'll go and cut up the Carpenter sisters
So you're using the fucking cameras
The cameras
And at the moment you're very
very cold
All right
douche bag
let's play
Cold
Heating up
Farmer
Warner
Alright
you know what
This is stupid
I'm going to hang up now
but you're getting warmer
Colder
Warner
Armor
You're on fire
Did you feel like an animal
Me too
But we have to finish the movie
Book yourself
Fuck about movies
I'm not aware when I do it again
Not in front of my eyes
So how are the new meds treating you
OK
I think
Still not seeing anyone I shouldn't be
What I'm really worried about though is Tara
I'm really worried about is you have been coming here for six months now and all we've really spoken about is how your sister isn't dealing with whatever happened to both of you a year ago
Now
you've alluded to an abusive relationship issues with your father
But every time I push you for specifics
you shut down
I have trust issues
OK
If I'm going to help you
I I
I need you to give me the details
OK
My father was Billy Lewis
He was a famous serial killer
They made a movie about it
Certainly last year I found out that my boyfriend was also a serial killer and only dating me because he idolized my father
Him and his psycho girlfriend killed a bunch of people
and when I got out that I'm Billy's daughter
this crazy rumor started online that I orchestrated the whole thing and framed them
Richie was my boyfriend
Well
you didn't
Of course
He almost killed my sister and me
Looking for a Stockton
OK
and how
How did you stop him
I stabbed him 22 times since let us throw
Then I shot him in the head
That's not why I'm here
Why are you here
Because
It felt right
I think we're done here
What
No
you said give you details
I'm just
I'm not equipped to deal with this kind of thing
Please
Doctor Stone
I'm asking for your help by law
Required to report this to the authorities
Report it
Report what
I didn't say I was gonna do anything
Not explicitly
no
You know what
Forget it
But just like all the others
Hey
Rich Cara
orange texting me
You know
you're supposed to pick up when I call
I got up therapy early
so I was thinking maybe we cooked dinner tonight
If you want
I'll see you soon
Hey
Tara
When
Are we being too loud
Not at all
Have you seen Tara
Don't be mad
Why would I be mad
Because you get mad
Is that Paul
I have found is about Freddy
OK
This one's yours
Thanks
Where's Tara
She went to the Omega Kappa Beta party
I begged her not to go to that
and we've now arrived at that
Do you know if she at least took her Taser
I cannot speak to how heavily armed Tara is at this fraternity party
Where are you coming back
baby
Ohh
cute boy
Shirtless again
Always you
Sweetie
it's been checking each other out for months
and I just talked to him because that right there is about all the romantic interaction I'm ready for
I'm going to go find Tara
OK
Be right back
Bye
It doesn't bother you
Being at a house party after you were almost brutally murdered at a house party
No
I think of it like being struck by lightning
You got it happening twice to the same person are extremely low
Guess I should stay close to you then
Hi
How you doing
T
You're lying
Those kids got some hard stuff in the kitchen
Frankie Sarah
Either way
no
not yet
I might brush it right
right
Where from
Michigan alright
you know what
I got a bottle of fireball in my room
Fuck it
Yeah
go
Ohh
I don't love that
Hey
you want to call it a night
No
I think that I'm actually still gonna hang
but you guys don't have to wait for me
Don't worry
I'll take care of you
I'm Frankie
and I'm spectacularly uninterested in knowing anything about you
No dude
Annika's not that bad
I appreciate you looking out for me
Alright
alright
cheers man for the dynamic dual 4
Tense tower
third floor
room 315
Yeah
We start making rules
get you out there
girls runner
She's gorgeous
right
Shut up
First look at you man
snapped and wrestling entire meal on your own
Hey excuse me
ohh my friend here
This is a snack right
It's not bad
Again
you need it
She's like girl involved in that stat sheet
No
that's a different firehead corner
The terrorists go down here
Turn riding Tessa
Yeah
you did
No
Chad
It's fine
I want to see Chad
Sometimes she wants to
Yeah
Sorry to interrupt
I'm just gonna tase you in the balls real quick
My hands on my sister
Fuck you
Are you fucking kidding me
You're stalking me now
It's that cycle
Tara
will you stop
I cannot believe you did that
You embarrassed me
That guy was a Dick
He was going to take advantage of you
So
It's why session
OK
so about you
I mean
you you're out of my life for five years
and then you can't leave me alone for 5 minutes because you're not dealing with what happened to us
Have you even gone to see the counselor once
No
I'm not going to
Why not
Because I'm uninterested in living in the past like you are
What's that supposed to mean
Hey
guys
I'm not going to let what happened to us for three days define the rest of my life
So you're just going to pretend it never happened
What are you doing here
Sam
In New York
when you you're working two shitty jobs
help with whatever boats your plan
I know what I'm going to do
OK
because I'm I'm gonna keep going to college
I'm gonna get my degree
and I'm gonna live my life
My life
Say I know
You just follow me here and you won't let me out of your sight
Just trying to lookout for you
I know
I know you are
He can't do it for the rest of my life
though
You have to let me go
Hey
murderer
She knows what she did
I didn't do anything
Walk away again
Yeah
I I I want tissues
I have like 3 tissues
Hey
I'm sorry I told Sam where you went
It's fun
just
She's on the way of mass
Like usual
I know what it's like when they hold on too tight
I'm sure you know
Lost my brother
My dad
Wouldn't leave me alone
He even transferred to the NYPD when I got to college
So stalker much
I'm gonna go let you guys check
Thank you
You can
Go back to your dorm
I'm pretty sure the fighting is done for the day
It's too bad it's actually looking forward to getting some shots at my camp
Yeah
yeah
bring it
Thank you
OK
now let me go up those stairs
Yeah
I don't know
I think I was just more messed up than I realized
Summers got to stick together
Insides you can do a lot better than date rape
Frankie
Tell me your
I think you're really special
I messed up anymore
Just so you know
My phone
Fuck you
What did you just say
I can't fuck you
No
I caught fucked you
didn't I
Please
immediately
All right
What do you what did you what did you need
My phone
So don't ever enter a room like that
Yeah
No
I'm gonna go get some rest
get sober
and please don't kill your sister
OK
She loves you very much
Goodnight
Hangouts
Yes
I say the most romantic things
Danny one
Can help it if my kink is woman is ashamed to be seen with me
you know it's not that I'm just
Not really
I know
Where your sister and your friends to know that you enjoy physical contact with another human being
I give you
I do
Your secret is safe with me
Little thing just now
It's not a big deal
I just can't help but notice that you're covered in Cherry Coke
I'm pretty sure it's dietary
Ohh
What
you don't like it
No
I love it
I do
It's been very sensual aerobatic choice
Is there another conspiracy nut
Being famous isn't all it's cracked up to be
And terrace pissed at me again
She says she wants me to let her go
Yeah
family can be rough
Sam
Get up here right now
I'm standing in front of the apartment
What's going on
Where the mutilated bodies of cute boy nice were discovered
Their names have just been released by police
Jason Carvey and Greg
Holy shit
that's that showed from our film studies Class 1 obsessed with Argento
This ghost based costumes
A character popularized by the stab movie franchise
Now this of course is pack a bag
We leave in 10
Sam
we're getting out of the city
What
Thank you very much
Suspicious
You're gonna think we go from here
Have a good night
Well
hold on
No
wait
Let's talk about this for a second
because this this might not have anything to do with us
Are you serious
It's a big city
It's Halloween
Everybody's wearing masks
This isn't a coincidence
You knew him
Barely
Chad
Mindy backed me up and there is a little bit close to home
See
When your dad's cock right
can you call him and find out what's going on before you make the unilateral decision to abandon my college education and flee the fucking state
I'm calling
Thank you
Who is it
Why did everyone just freak out when her phone rang
You gotta keep up with it
Sam
Right
Happens to talk to you
Mr
Bailey
hi
I have
and I was actually just about to call you
My sister thinks I'm probably overreacting
Unfortunately
you're not
What do you mean
What's going on
I'm afraid I need you to come down to the station
Sounds
Hold out
Tara
No
Get back inside
Lock the door
Are you serious now
You don't want to stick together
Fine
What the fuck
I never deleted his contact
This is coming from his number
Don't pick that up
Just let her in
Sam
Who is this
Hello
Samantha
Did you miss me
I want you to think long and hard about whether you really want to do this because the last two people that fucked with us ended up dead
You should be thanking me
Sam
Jason and Greg were gonna kill you and your sister
I got enough before they had the chance
So what
You're protecting us now
Not quite
I'm going to show the world who you really are
A lot
I'm going to punish you
Sam
You shouldn't believe everything you read on the Internet
asshole
Don't be cute
You're gonna pay for what you did
And I'm not gonna stop until I butchered you
And you and anyone who gets between us
You and Tara better watch your back
You better watch yours
On Monday
Yes
You got a problem here
guy
Right
I want the back
Thank you
It's locked
This was found next to the body at the apartment crime scene
DNA says that if long as someone named Richie Kirsch
That ringing bell
We're familiar with him
but the one that attacked us had a different mask on
It was kind of more beat up
like it was older
Kind of ask
Do malibus for earlier tonight
How's that
A party with my friends
I was at my therapist
I can give you his information
You can call to check if you want
And then I met Tara at that party where I'd taste someone
Unrelated
Is that before or after this happened
Before the point is we are with people
so our roommates dad
Just happened to pull our case
That'd be a crazy coincidence
right
Yeah
The detective who had the case
he offered it to me
Music
goals
Quinn
But I can totally give it back
If you're uncomfortable
it's up to you
It's fine
So if the man who attacked you did steal your license and planted next to the body
And it probably be somebody close to you
I wanna be on your friends when we moved here with Mindy and Chad for summer semester like six months ago
so
Quinn
Ethan
Annika ostenson
They can't get involved for Quinn
so that's one less we have to worry about
Do either of you have anyone that might want to target
Not only when he's alive
Yikes
FBI is here claiming jurisdiction
Where are they
Can I help you
Especially during FBI
I work out of the Atlanta office
You're too big for residents of my city
Before they moved here for college
I've been investigating their online activity for the past few months
Take a special interest and ghost face
attacks Kirby
Hey
Sam
Alright
Tara
you're the FBI
There's no issue there
Yeah
we went to Woodsboro high together
She was a senior when I was a freshman
We share a certain history
Yeah
but I'm not trying to get into a jurisdictional pissing contest here
I just want to help
I'll show you mine
etcetera
This mask at the bodega team and traces of two individuals
Charlie Walker
Joe Roberts
both deceased
These killers of 2011
Charlie Walker gave me this
Like I said
I take a special interest
Is this the mess he was wearing when he attacked you
No
He's leaving them on purpose
which means whoever's doing this is a student of the killers who came before
Maybe he believes Sam's the latest in a long line
Yeah
good luck with that
I'm sorry
that's not possible
You're both persons of interest in a double homicide
so you're not allowed to leave town
Sorry
are you serious
He's right
But if we work together
we're going
You have an alibi
Just saying
your sister
Sarah
Weathers
Channel 4
Do you ladies think you're the reason the Ghostface killer has come to the Big Apple
Nice try sweetie
but I've done this dance before
Ohh
Stay away from us
Are you really still mad at me
You said you wouldn't write a book about what happened
and then you wrote a book about what happened
Come on
somebody was going to write about it
That's what I do
I know if you could tell the movie rights
it's it's all about true Crime limited series these days after everything we went through together
What would you rethink
That's a low blow
So was your book
You called me unstable and a born killer
That's taken out of context
That's literally a quote
You don't think what you wrote has something to do with what's happening to us
Come on
Hey
I talked to Sydney
She's not coming here
is she
No
She sends her love
but she's taking Mark and the kids someplace safe
She deserves to have her happy ending
And not much
we agree
Hey
I want to catch this fucker as much as you do
Maybe
Or maybe you're just afraid that without ghost face in your life
you're going to fade away
Danger
Where's that
You're a day early for trick or treating
you know
Listen up
It's terrifying as this all is
I'm actually glad I get a
Calling the killers last time
It's fine
OK
the way I see it
someone is out to make a sequel to the Requel
What's that
Raquel
You're beautiful
sweetie
Let's hold questions to the end
Stab one took place in Woodsboro
Step two took place in college
Do we think that the killer is trying to copy the movies
That is one possibility
Heroes now in college
Check
Suspicious new characters brought in to round out the suspect list
and
Or body count
Check
check and check
I don't like this
I can't just be about Step 2
Why not
It would make sense if this were just a sequel
but we're not in a sequel because nobody just makes sequels anymore
We're in a franchise
and there are certain rules to a continuing franchise
I had a feeling rule one
Everything is bigger than last time
Bigger budget
bigger cast
bigger body count
longer chases
Shootouts
beheading to that atop what came before to keep people coming back
Beheadings
beheadings
rule 2
Whatever happened last time
expect the opposite
Franchises only survived by subverting expectations if the killers last time were whiny snowflake film nerds with Letterboxed accounts instead of personalities
You can bet the opposite will be true here and Rule 3 no one is safe
Legacy characters
Cannon fodder at this point
usually brought back only to be killed off in some cheap bid for nostalgia
It's not looking too good for Galen Kirby
Ohh
And that's not even the worst part
This is the problem
she tells us
The worst part
The worst part is franchises are just continuing episodic installments designed to boost an IP
which means main characters are completely expendable now too
Laurie Strode
Nancy Thompson
Ellen Ripley
Sally Hardesty
Jigsaw
Tony Stark
James Bond
I mean
even Luke Skywalker all died so their franchises could live on
That means it's not just a friend group
Any of us could go at any time
Especially Sam and Tara
Agree with any of us this and am I in the front room
Am I like one of the targets of
Am I going to diverge
That was a weird overshare
but it brings us to our current suspects
Ethan
A shy
dorky guy who no one suspects because he's so shy and dorky
OK
wait
what
Why am I on the suspect list
Because I'm randomly Chad's roommate
Roommate
Lotteries can be juked
You could have fixed it to get next to us
Glenn
The slutty roommate
a horror movie
Classic sex positive
but thank you
Umm
how did you come to live with Sam and Tara
I answered their ad online
OK
say no more
You've already implicated yourself enough
It was an anonymous ad
Mindy
and you know
we vetted her
Plus
her dad is a cop
and that makes it more likely that she's the killer
because having a cop dad is a great coverage
Do you not remember how these movies work
Tara
She always liked this and finally Annika
Never trust the love interest
OK
So we have our rules and we have our suspects
So wait
wait
what about you guys
I mean
I think it's pretty safe to rule out the four of us who went through this last year in Woodsboro
Not agreed
What if the trauma you all went through caused one or or more of you to snap
Yeah
or the fame you got from the killings made you thirsty for more
I mean
let's be honest here
some of the theories online about Sam are don't you fucking dare
OK
she's right though
I mean
if face facts
if we're all suspects
you're all set
Remember Samantha Carpenter's alibi therapist was stabbed to death doesn't nose through the nose and my stuff is that
It's pretty messed up
He turned her in for making threatening remarks
ended up dead
and guess which patients notes were stolen
So Sam kills her own Alba and steals her own session notes
Another mask was found at the scene
It's a DNA match for Roman Bridger Ghostface
who was directing Step 3
It's like he's leaving us real life franchise Easter eggs
Dropping the village mass in reverse
Almost like he's counting down to something
What happens when he gets to one
So we've had nine Ghostface killers so far
alright
but I thought in the movies forget about the movies
and movies don't
We look last year was Amber Freeman and Richie Kirsch
whose mass we found at the first crime scene
along with the bodies of two film students who killed the professor earlier that same night
That it was Jill Roberts and Charlie Walker
There's a bodega
Roman Bridger was the only single ghost face
Kudos to him for ambition
His mask was found at the strikes
It's just leaves
Mickey Altieri
Nancy Loomis Demarker #1
the father of our chief suspect
Whoever is doing this is leading us back to Sam
I will check in later and tell your daughter to stay sharp proximity to the carpenter's proximity to go space
Hey
Jack
Call the Atlanta Field office
Pick up what you can on Agent Reid
I think you should get out of the city
you know
considering what happened to you last time
I wouldn't blame you if
You want
It's very thoughtful of you
but
I don't think I'm going anywhere
Will you 2 just make out already
That is so inappropriate
you know
whatever
In Overwatch
hey
go down
Yeah
we do not have to stay here
Well
too bad
I insist
Safety in numbers should be so fun
Little slumber party with the Core 4
Core four
Yeah
Did you just give us a nickname
Well
I sure did
I mean
we've been through a lot together
and it's pretty cool
Nickname
That's debatable
It's extremely debatable
You can't just give yourself a nickname
dingus
Of course I can
because I just did core 4 up top
No
don't get that away from me
Please
for the love of God
don't do it
You know
I would actually like one more respect and support from my fellow
Listen to the guys
What the hell
We're hearing from sources inside the homicide division of the prime suspect is not
That's Samantha Carpenter
one of the survivors
No killings in 2022
seen here attacking a woman on the street last
Problem with
In the wake of the
Last year
The Carpenter was
When
Version
I know you're not a fan of the way that I've been handling things
And then I've been doing a really hard time
But I can't say that
None of us can relate to what you are experiencing
And I'm really
really sorry that you have to do that
It's not your fault
And I know I shouldn't care what people think
Sucks being this hated
Hey
hey
Choose to reminder not a single person in this room hates you
OK
we have have been through some fucked up stuff and we are coping with it differently
I mean
we moved here together for one very specific reason
We're a team
We are
The core function
Thank you very much
I hate you
That's what I'm talking about before saying it
No
I'm not gonna say it now
I've been sleeping with cute boy from across the hall
I don't know
I knew it
Yeah
from the day you're out
Sales of the ghost things Halloween mask across the tri-state area in the last 24 hours have gone through the roof
I've got my mask
What about you
Jay
You know
it sure is going to be one spooky house
I'll say
Now let's get over to dinner with her
Yeah
I know she's my roommate
but you're like the police
Yeah
I know
What's up
bitch
Sir
Samantha
I feel like we should have five or something
The core 4I don't call it that
but we'll do
You know
That was really
She's really freaked out and paranoid
No
and don't use my good face wash
It's pH balance for women
Pick up your phone
baby
That was really no way
Hey
not right now
Your intentions
No
it's fine
I'll call him back
OK
God
Oh my God wanted her gentleman call her back at it again
Run
Fuck
Stop that
I left them inside
Fuck
She's got you
No
The internal forces
Somebody stole the door
Soon
You can't tell me
Say something more positive
Come on
let's go
Let's go
You've got you
Can't do it
What
You have to go right now
OK
This isn't your fault
Better
Someone took our knives
So we couldn't fight back
I don't know who I can trust
Then don't trust anyone and friends
Not me
Not anymore
I have a few more questions for you
Check
We're working
What
When
Last night
But I icon
You know this
man
You disappear
My sister almost gets killed
Dude
I was in a study hall with 100 other people
You can ask any of them
No
Oh my God
Two Annika Quinn
Mandy
I'm so sorry
Step the fuck back
You're at the top of my list
I had econ
Be right back
I'm really sorry about
Thank you
But my kids are coming
Might help him
They took me off the case
I'm not gonna stop till I find
You fuck with my family
You die
Agreed
OK
You OK
I came as soon as I heard Dale
I swear to God
No truth
OK
I'm
I'm here for whatever you need
OK
Nice try
Really
I am
OK
fine
Off the record
OK
Thank you
I mean
sorry I punched you
No
you're not
I'm not
You're the cop
right
I did some digging on your first two victims and I found something
I know where the masks are coming from
Show me
ladies
Herbie
She's with the FBI
She's a child
When did they start letting children into the FBI
On 30
Well
you look like a zygote
I have a gun
Gale
OK
fine
You're going to want to see this
too
Jason and Greg were little Atlanta bitch boys
Apparently they used fake names to make this place
How did you find it
It's called investigative journalism for a reason
How didn't you find it
Weren't you tracking them
I went through their financial records dozens of times and this was not in any of them
This makes sense
Don't worry
I'm just really good at my job
Don't get there
What is this place
What's with all the security
It's movie theater
It's not just a theater
It's a shrine
I thought the whole God damn franchise
Chad
This is uncle Randy's
We've gotten everything
Because then if I was stabbed with you all have been through so much
Motril Motril allies
How did they get all this stuff
I mean
isn't this evidence
Well
cops like money and evidence can get lost pretty easily
Present company excluded
of course
Why am I here exactly
My alibi checks out so I can keep an eye on you
roomie
The killer must have found this place before he murdered Jason and Greg
and then he took the mask off the mannequins
All nine
from Stu and Billy to Amber and Richard
God damn
how fucking cool is this place
Fuck no
Fuck yes
Come on Sam
You got to be excited to get our murder on again together
Billy and Sam's team Loomis
I'm ready to slice up more motherfuckers
What are you doing
I don't know
So somebody killed these chuckle fucks and
Took over
Took over someone who believes that Sam masterminded Woodsboro
If this were a normal staff movie
this would be the killer Slayer
Which means this isn't normal Stevie
TV that tilts too much her if you believe he's dead
I hear you're a horror fan
it's been said
Best nightmare on Elm Street
The original
Best friend at the 13th Part 2 chapter
Had a crush on Corey Feldman
OK
respect
Psycho two is underrated
Candyman the original or equal both
OK
Game recognize game
So when do I get to be a normal person again
I don't want to be a part of this
I don't want to be a part of some stupid legacy because because of me
I'm sorry
Stop it
Tara
I got her
That seemed intense
Persons I came back into her life
I just
I made a mess of it
Where's your mother and all this
She cut me off when I told Tara about Billy
Then Tara cut her off because she wouldn't talk to me
So
No
neither of us have a mother
I'm sorry to say this
but fuck her
my parents said too
But you can still make your own family
even if it's just with one person
If you lose that one person
They just you keep going
Maybe you find another loaner and you look after each other
How did you get past what happened to you
I almost died after I was stabbed
Technically
I did die for four minutes
When I recovered
I got mad
I didn't want to spend the rest of my life being afraid of monsters
I wanted the monsters to be afraid of me
You're like that
Sorry to interrupt
I think I might have an idea about how to turn the tables on this screen
Yeah
we're in
Sorry
GAIL
No press allowed
Police business
I'm good at my job too
You should have stayed with the others
It's not going to happen
There's no point in both of us putting ourselves at risk
No
I'm back up
So we're really doing the phone tracing thing that never works in the movies
It'll be all keep him talking
Sam
Two more minutes
I've almost got him
And then he hangs up
Just before we can get a lock
I can trace a call
And under 15 seconds
Well
you've got them out there as baked because the killer usually calls from somewhere nearby
And you think they're safe because it's broad daylight in a public place
Look
I am here
OK
And so is Bailey
This is exactly how our Uncle Randy died
Broad daylight
Public place changed into a van
Step
step
No more Randy
Hey
Sam
frosty out there OK
we're good
You're going to die
You know you're gonna die
Samantha
choking on your own blood
How will I hack up your sister
If we find you first for a mastermind
you're not very bright
Waiting for me to call
desperately hoping I'm nearby so the police can grab me
But I'm not nearby
I'm a step ahead
Be seeing you
Samantha
Did you get it
Yep
geolocation coming through right now
Listen the Upper West Side
This building halfway across the city and W 96
How did you know that
OK
No press pitch
Last time I saw you
you were in Glee club
Forgive me if I don't trust you to keep them safe
You go
baby
Thanks
My friend Tony works on the Upper West Side
Can you get there quicker before you can finish her off
Possible
He's gonna tell her we have to get there now
No
it's true
We don't have a minute now
You have to trust me
We gotta make the right call
Get in
get in
Hey
get out of my car
You think you're doing
It's an official vehicle
Hey
should we use the sentence
Did you really think we're going to see this car now
Car
You can't steal a cop car
That would be our food
Hello
Not the food
it's for you
Who is it
Ask who's calling
please
He says it's the killer
Hello
Hello GAIL
it's strange that you and I have never spoken on the phone
This is long overdue
I agree
I figured after all these years you'd want an interview
You figured right
So what's your motive this time
Are you angry at the movies or you just trying to stay relevant
I could ask you the same don't you know the legacy characters are disposable now
Nobody cares about last centuries heroes and why bother with me at all
Call it nostalgia
Or maybe you deserve to be punished for all that money you made off the misery of others
Maybe it's time someone made a buck reporting your death
You know you're like the 10th guy to try this
right
And spoiler alert
It never works out for the dipshit in the mask
Oh
but they certainly leave a mark before they go
don't they
Richie and Amber managed to butcher Dewey
carved him up like a Christmas goose
How does it feel to lose the only man who ever loved you
Fuck you
How does it feel to know that you weren't there for him at the end
Not there to give him comfort as he died screaming in his own God
You're the one who's gonna die screaming
maybe
but you won't be around to see it
You couldn't stop what happened to Dewey
Just like you're not going to be able to stop this
How's that for nostalgia
fucker
You missed
Sure I did
You win
I'm in the elevator heading for the ground floor
Sure you are
You just had me
Maybe I'm wound
Or maybe I'm wearing a bulletproof vest
That's why I'm going to shoot you in the fucking head
You would have made a good killer Gale
Sydney never would have made sense and Dewey was the fan favorite
but you cracking under the pressure and turning into Ghost Face would have been a great twist
Keep talking
asshole
What do you want to talk about
You never got to be the leading lady
did you
It was always all about poor sweet Sydney sucking up all the oxygen
Where did that leave you to be
The brains and the sex appeal
Sorry about your boyfriend
All those muscles didn't help much
Can you hold please
Huh
Fuck you
OK
Yeah
Help
I'm
I should know
but he was
Didn't get
Tell Sydney
Never go
GAIL
please
Other way
other way
Give them back
Please
please
They need to right now
Hold in
Right away
Got a big pulse
Get the backboard
We need to move now
Stop
Let's move
I got used faces
Did you
You scared you guys
I really don't want to get hurt again
And they do it
Don't want you getting hurt again either
no
So what are we doing now
Maybe he gets to win this time
He wants to punish me
Me
So maybe they let him
I'll just give myself up
If this is what I have to do
To keep you safe
It's worth it
No
we're not doing that
So
all right
you went back to Woodsboro
That protect me every single day
You make the decision to protect me
None of us would even be alive if it weren't for you
You have to let us protect you this time
Yes
We're A-Team
remember
Actually
Her family
Let's go
Core 4
Come on
just one more
core one
It's a nice thing
This kind of keep coming after us
Isn't there somewhere like safe we could just hold up in
Just gonna keep finding this
We could use that though
I'm getting my ass chewed out for not dropping the case
and now you want me to do what you want to lure him to secure location and travel inside
Then what
We execute them
It can help us
Let's kill this son of a bitch
I'm stuck here
But you'll give us the key cards to the theater instead of having surveillance and security cameras
But we can use that against him
I can go ahead and remember traveling public
more people around you left
Fancy has to take a shot at you before you get there
This is even a good plan
We don't have to come if you don't want to just peel off
And the killer picks us off 1 by 1
No
thank you
Just get them here
Come on in here
Yes
because it will be much less scary in serial killer movie theater
Yeah
Let's go
Ghostface
ghostface
Train to South Carolina
Where's Mindy
She missed the train
Track me on let's try to keep us together
pulling us apart
It's OK
It's fine
She's with you
Then she made us there
How many steps do we have
Track
Is
Sorry
Going to community
Eyes
Fuck you
Very well
This is especially late in center
Mindy
Fuck
Help somebody help
Are you OK
Come on
Sorry
call 911
Oh
my God
Are you OK
Yeah
So good
You're gonna be OK
God damn it
I got it wrong again
Medical assistance at 66th St
Hey
it's up to Bailey
I've got everything set up
Where
Minion Ethan
the five minutes behind us
Let's get you all inside
Not you
Don't trust anyone
Remember
we don't know you
We don't know you
Not really
You're not woodsboro
I'm sorry
It's OK
I get it
OK
You too
Good call
I cleared the whole place before he got here
So this is the only way in or out
He steps in through the first door
both doors lock
automatically trapping him inside
We turned it into a killbox
weapons
one gun and I hold on to it
I am the only one with a badge here
and that's the way it's gonna be
We're safe here
I'm going to check in with Mindy
see if they're close
Hey
You know you're not safe here
Whenever someone says we're safe here
it means you're not
Not now
You're smarter than this
Sam
Grab a weapon and clear this place yourself
You know I'm right
Excellent choice
My favorite
Curvy
Kirby
Hello
Get everyone out of there
Say you're not safe
I heard from the Atlanta Field office
They said agent three
They said Agent Reed's been on a downward spiral ever since the Woodsboro murders last year
What are you talking about
They fired Kirby two months ago for being mentally unstable
She's no longer with the FBI
Use this place so old
I'm sorry
you can
you can have just
No
I mean
listen if you want to
They're like 100 years old
Maybe that's your thing
I actually
And maybe we are saying look up on her to do that
Yeah
you should have done that a lot sooner
You could also do it like a lot more time
Let's go
That's not come on track
She made this whole theater killbots for us
Hey
what about that
There's an exit door
Maybe it leads to the roof or something
There's only one way to find out
Let's go
Hello
Come on
Go
Ready
I need you to be ready
You ready
Giving
Come on
Say the fuck back
We know it's you
Kirby
Home
One of them knocked me out
What are you doing
Did you kill you
Kill my daughter
Whatever he's been saying to you
don't listen to him
He's probably the killer
Great job
Of you
You of course me
Frankly
I expected more from the two of you after what you did to us
What do you mean us
Mindy was right
It was easy to drop the roommate lottery
I mean
all I had to do to meet you was room with the conceited
condescending alpha
literally named Chad
Fuck
It felt good to kill him
This is your grandmother
Sam
Nancy Loomis really runs in fucking family
doesn't it
Speaking of family
wait for it
My names
not Ethan Landry
isn't that
Dad
wait
If it's you two that just leaves
Mindy
You didn't see that one coming to dance
Yeah
because you die
You've kind of done it so
There's a good way to get off the suspect list
Stab kill
Weathers staff meeting on the train
that sort of thing
Yep
and I just made sure I was first on the scene so I could switch your body up with the freshman
A little fake blood prosthetic
You'd be amazed at what a grieving father can get away with
Christmas
It was my favorite
That's #3
That's two
These
Your fathers
This is what we've been counting down to
Sam
I'm gonna need you to put it on
Don't you
What is this
You did this as a family
Hell yeah
Bitch
You should know better than anyone they're still not getting it
Look
I don't know what you believe
but I didn't commit those murders in Woodsboro
It wasn't me
We know that
Of course you did
What do you think this is based on some bullshit conspiracy theory
Come on
who do you think started the rumors about you in the first place
You know how easy it was to turn Sam from the hero of Woodsboro into the villain
How easy it is to convince the world to believe the worst in people rather than the best
Because it's not enough to just kill someone these days
you have to assassinate the character first
So when dad here discovers you're horribly mutilated body post with Sam where her father's mask
he'll say some port on bastard right on the Internet that you're the real ghost face and took matters into their own diluted hands
Exactly
That's why it's the perfect alibi and all the best lies based on the truth
Near a killer
just like your father
No
I'm not
Yes
you are
You motherfucker
You killed our brother
What are you talking about
You said your brother died in a car accident
No
no
Just something
He died in Woodsboro
Hands of your bitch sister
You're Richie's family
Yeah
Now
it wasn't until I saw that photograph of what you actually done to him that I knew and I knew you had to fucking die
You have to be punished along with anyone else who stands in our way
There she is
There's the fucking killer over parenting job
by the way
Shut your whore fucking mouth
I've got a perfect dad
No
And then maybe overindulge Richie's love of these little movies
Maybe
For me
they're just a little dark
We should
Really
He made a few of his own
Did you know
So you guys are thinking
Nice
There's a very special bond between a father and his first son
Which is why I helped him build this collection
This
On his yes is a very passionate collector
He inspired others
We had to kill those two wannabe film students because well
We have to kill you first
huh
I put the theater in their name
Then good old Detective Bailey would have just stumbled on it
But I didn't have to
because by golly
that GAIL Weathers is 1 hell of a journalist
I built a tribute to my son
Which is why this is where you have to die
Sam
Surrounded by all the things he loved the most
What happens next
What
After you're done with us
you just disappear
No
I've gotta hurry over to the hospital
Make sure Mindy and GAIL don't pull through
because everybody dies
Everyone who had anything to do with the death of my son suffers and dies
Beyond the mask
He was
Sup
That's not true
Yeah
Your son
He was a man baby who made his girlfriend do all the killing
He was a strong federal young man
He was a limp Dick little fuck who cried before he slit his throat
OK
Recognize this
Yeah
Alright
I kind of need this
Are you gonna do about it
bitch
Find Sam
I'll get help
Careful
Stick something in you
Tara
Out
You guys are so fucked now
Sam
Yeah
let me go
No
Sam
come on
Trust me
Pico
Yeah
I'll tell you a fucking virgin
Looks like you're down another brother
Always got to shoot him in the head
Hello
Detective Bailey
I've got one question for you
What's that
What's your favorite scary movie
Favorite game
I'm asking because you're in one now
You're a fine movie
Ohh
I see you've put on your true face
Your birthright
Poetic that you're going to die in it
This is what you wanted
isn't it
Now you know the truth
huh
Murder is in your blood
Stop fucking around and show yourself
What you wish for
All right
I'm a fucking police officer
How do you think this is gonna go
Sam
Who do you think they're gonna believe
Probably the one who's still alive
Hi
No
My father was a murderer
What you think
Better than that
Call
Thank you
How you doing
Fuck with myself
Nice
Thanks
You agree
Hmm
Thank you for letting me go
I know you could take care of yourself
I want to be in your life
But only as much as you want me to be
I want you to be
Everybody
I'm gonna get so much therapy after that
I'm serious
We're going to get through this
Together
So that no scary movie once
I thought you might need some reinforcements
and I called Mount Sinai and Mindy
Angela going to be OK
He's on the way here now
They couldn't stop her
All right
You ever need me call
We're all part of the same fucked up family
you know
and legacy doesn't always have to be a bad thing
OK
Hey
It's Chad
We got another one here
Jack
come on
Your life
Looking for
You probably need that
Hillary
it's even Amberley and Quinn and Quinn
Fuck
Don't miss the long again
OK
Oh my God
We all survived
Twist drafted
by the way
Coming